# **Ayoub Mouloua**

## Cybersecurity Consultant

 Casablanca, Morocco
 ■ contact@ayoub0x1.com
 +212645469366
 ■ Moroccan
 ■ B
 in ayoub0x1
 ayoub0x1

 □ ayoub0x1#4552
 ★ Ayoub0x1
 ♦ https://app.hackthebox.com/profile/803489
 ★ https://ayoub0x1.me

#### **₽** PROFILE

Skilled Cybersecurity student with expertise in risk management, unauthorized access, viruses, managing networks, server administration, deploying and monitoring SIEM, and a wide range of vulnerabilities and threats. Well-versed in direct and remote analysis with strong critical thinking, communication, and people skills.

## **EDUCATION**

**42** Associate degree, 1337, 1337 school
IT training in several fields: Information security, programming, networking...

Sep 2019 – present

**English literature,** *Moulay Ismail University* English Studies as a second major

Meknes, Morocco

Sep 2021 - present

Khouribga, Morocco

**Baccalaureate**, *Manfalouti high school*Baccalaureate degree in physics and chemistry

Sep 2016 – Jun 2019 Meknes, Morocco

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### Cybersecurity Consultant, CapValue

• External & Internal Penetration Testing

Jun 2022 – present Casablanca, Morocco

- Web Application Penetration Testing
- Mobile Application Penetration Testing
- Report writing

#### Bug Bounty Hunter, HackerOne

Apr 2020 – present Remote

Participated in many public and private bug bounty programs through the responsible disclosure of security vulnerabilities in various web technologies and applications to high-profile organizations. Some statistics include but are not limited to:

• Found and Reported several security vulnerabilities and got fixed.

Over 20 acknowledgments were received (U.S. Dept Of Defense, AT&T, IBM, Semrush, Moneybird, Automattic, Hyatt Hotels, etc.).

• Reference: hackerone.com/ayoub0x1

## ⊗ SKILLS

Programming & Scripting • • • • • Web Penetration Test

C/C++/Python/Bash Manual/Automation Audit, vulnerability assessment

Networking SIEM / SOC

Routing, Network security Elastic stack, Prometheus

## PUBLICATIONS

#### CVE-2022-2365, zadam

Description: CWE-79 Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting')

Product: zadam/trilium

Versions Affected: <0.53.3: affects versions prior to 0.53.3

#### (6) LANGUAGES

Arabic • • • • English • • • •

#### **CERTIFICATES**

Introduction to Cybersecurity

Cisco

**Networking Essentials** 

Cisc

contact@ayoub0x1.com 1/1